[
    {
        "question": "ارثر",
        "answer": "ارثر"
    },
    {
        "question": "انجيلو",
        "answer": "انجيلو"
    },
    {
        "question":"آليا",
        "answer": "آليا"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبي",
        "answer": "روبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "آي",
        "answer": "آي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "answer": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسكي",
        "answer": "ساسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساكورا",
        "answer": "ساكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاكاشي",
        "answer": "كاكاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاشي",
        "answer": "ايتاشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "answer": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "answer": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "answer": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "answer": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "answer": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "تشوبر",
        "answer": "تشوبر"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "answer": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غون",
        "answer": "غون"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيلوا",
        "answer": "كيلوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورابيكا",
        "answer": "كورابيكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليوريو",
        "answer": "ليوريو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "answer": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "answer": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "answer": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "آرمين",
        "answer": "آرمين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريوك",
        "answer": "ريوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "لايت",
        "answer": "لايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "إل",
        "answer": "إل"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميلو",
        "answer": "ميلو"
    },
    {
        "question": "إدوارد",
        "answer": "إدوارد"
    },
    {
        "question": "ألفونس",
        "answer": "ألفونس"
    },
    {
        "question": "وينري",
        "answer": "وينري"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماي",
        "answer": "ماي"
    },
    {
        "question": "رين",
        "answer": "رين"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوكي",
        "answer": "يوكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانامي",
        "answer": "كانامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "زيرو",
        "answer": "زيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيكارو",
        "answer": "هيكارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاورو",
        "answer": "كاورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاروهي",
        "answer": "هاروهي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاماكي",
        "answer": "تاماكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيون",
        "answer": "كيون"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاروهي سوزوميا",
        "answer": "هاروهي سوزوميا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينجي",
        "answer": "شينجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ري",
        "answer": "ري"
    },
    {
        "question": "أسكا",
        "answer": "أسكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ماكوتو",
        "answer": "ماكوتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيرو",
        "answer": "هيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "دوروثي",
        "answer": "دوروثي"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوجي",
        "answer": "يوجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غوجو",
        "answer": "غوجو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "answer": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميغومي",
        "answer": "ميغومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تودو",
        "answer": "تودو"
    },
    {
        "question": "سابتورا",
        "answer": "سابتورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جينتوكي",
        "answer": "جينتوكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاجورا",
        "answer": "كاجورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينباشي",
        "answer": "شينباشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تاكاسوغي",
        "answer": "تاكاسوغي"
    }
]
